<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<Topics>
	<Topic Name="MISC_FIRST_CONTACT">
		<Dialogue>
			<Speaker Name="Drengin">1</Speaker>
			<Listener Name="Human">0</Listener>
			<Phrase>
				<Morality>2</Morality>
				<Text>We have you on the run, [YourLeaderName]. Not even this hypothetical shielding technology will be enough to save your putrid hide.

We WILL find Beta Prime, we WILL destroy your research, and we will FINALLY put an end to your withering species.</Text>
			</Phrase>
		</Dialogue>
		<Dialogue>
			<Speaker Name="Altarian">2</Speaker>
			<Listener Name="Human">0</Listener>
			<Phrase>
				<Morality>0</Morality>
				<Text>Shielding technology could easily turn the war in our favor, cousin.
You and your scientists work on the technology... we'll take care of the Drengin.</Text>
			</Phrase>
		</Dialogue>
		<Dialogue>
			<Speaker Name="Arcean">3</Speaker>
			<Listener Name="Human">0</Listener>
			<Phrase>
				<Morality>1</Morality>
				<Text>We are here to help, [YourLeaderName]. Your scientists will be safe with the Arcean army protecting them.</Text>
			</Phrase>
		</Dialogue>
	</Topic>
	<Topic Name="AI_WELCOME_DEFENDING_WINNING_HATE">
		<Dialogue>
			<Speaker Name="Drengin">1</Speaker>
			<Listener Name="Human">0</Listener>
			<Phrase>
				<Morality>2</Morality>
				<Text>Beta Prime is in our cross-hairs. We've been sharpening our teeth on our previous battles against you. Prepare to feel the true bite of the Drengin army.

#How's that shielding technology coming along? Not so well, eh? Stupid humans... always relying on their pitiful technology.

#The Drengin Army is massing on your borders... and not even your precious Shield technology can save you from oblivion.

#[YourLeaderName]... you were kind enough to share Hyperdrive technology, then foolish enough to use it against us. Not even this rumored Shield technology can save you.

#Prepare for the fall of Beta Prime and the extinction of the human race.</Text>
			</Phrase>
		</Dialogue>
	</Topic>
	<Topic Name="AI_WELCOME_DEFENDING_LOSING_HATE">
		<Dialogue>
			<Speaker Name="Drengin">1</Speaker>
			<Listener Name="Human">0</Listener>
			<Phrase>
				<Morality>2</Morality>
				<Text>So, the humans still have some tricks up their sleeve... be on guard, [YourLeaderName], for Beta Prime will fall.

#Pitiful human... you've been lucky thus far, but soon your luck will run out.


No precious Shield technology will save you then.

#Shields will only save you for so long, Human. Our scientists are hard at work on stonger, more advanced weaponry that will bring you to your knees.

#Why are you here, human? I suggest you round up troops to protect your scientists on Beta Prime... trust me, they are in extreme danger.

#Beta Prime won't be safe until you've taken out all of my troops. And trust me, human, I won't make it easy.</Text>
			</Phrase>
		</Dialogue>
	</Topic>
	<Topic Name="AI_SCOFF_AT_BRIBE">
		<Dialogue>
			<Speaker Name="Drengin">1</Speaker>
			<Listener Name="Human">0</Listener>
			<Phrase>
				<Morality>2</Morality>
				<Text>Why would you give me this? It takes more than a bribe to stop the Drengin army from taking Beta Prime.

#You've gone mad! Your gifts will not keep us from defeating you again... your forces will fall like before, only this time our victory will be all-encompassing. The human race will die... only now with less toys.</Text>
			</Phrase>
		</Dialogue>
	</Topic>
</Topics>