<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" standalone="yes"?>
<Topics>
	<Topic Name="MISC_FIRST_CONTACT">
		<Dialogue>
			<Speaker Name="Yor">5</Speaker>
			<Listener Name="Human">0</Listener>
			<Phrase>
				<Morality>2</Morality>
				<Text>Human, the Yor army has recently been outfitted with Hyperdrive-equipped missile weaponry. These ships will easily cut through your shield technology, leaving your forces in ruin.

Extermination awaits, [YourLeaderName].</Text>
			</Phrase>
		</Dialogue>
		<Dialogue>
			<Speaker Name="Iconian">9</Speaker>
			<Listener Name="Human">0</Listener>
			<Phrase>
				<Morality>0</Morality>
				<Text>The galaxy is in turmoil, [YourLeaderName]. The evil Dread Lord armada has been released, the Yor have developed and launched deadly new warships, and the Drengin forces gather and strengthen.

We must put this dark hour behind us, human - the Iconian army is ready to fight!</Text>
			</Phrase>
		</Dialogue>
	</Topic>
	<Topic Name="AI_WELCOME_DEFENDING_WINNING_HATE">
		<Dialogue>
			<Speaker Name="Yor">5</Speaker>
			<Listener Name="Human">0</Listener>
			<Phrase>
				<Morality>1</Morality>
				<Text>Calculations indicate you will have a difficult time defeating us, human. Your shield technology will do little to save your forces against our new weaponry.
#The Dread Lords are an ancient civilization from our time, [YourLeaderName]. They were the ones that taught us the weak nature of biological beings. Their return marks the end of the human race.

There is little you can do to change this.</Text>
			</Phrase>
		</Dialogue>
	</Topic>
	<Topic Name="AI_WELCOME_DEFENDING_LOSING_HATE">
		<Dialogue>
			<Speaker Name="Yor">5</Speaker>
			<Listener Name="Human">0</Listener>
			<Phrase>
				<Morality>1</Morality>
				<Text>Your forces are stronger than we expected. We will have to strengthen our missiles to couter-balance this.
#Our Hyperdrive-equipped missiles should be more efficient against your vessels. Apparently we miscalculated your military might.
#We calculated the skill of your army based on your past military failures. Apparently you've improved since last fighting our Drengin allies.</Text>
			</Phrase>
		</Dialogue>
	</Topic>
</Topics>